It took me all night to get back on my feet.
Every bit of what Iori said is true.
She has every right to be upset, and I've got no right to talk back.
I knew I was being selfish,
but I didn't want to hate myself, so I pretended not to notice.
Still, Nagase could've chosen her words.
Inaba, get to the club room and do some work!
We need to finish this before dead week!
Oh, sorry! Taichi's with me. We'll be there soon.
Hurry!
Shall we?
Yeah.
Club activities are on hold starting tomorrow!
And the presentation is the week after!
We're completely out of time!
I want to study, too!
If I end up failing, you and Inaba had better do something about it!
You're responsible for your own grades.
It's not like only a day's worth of studying will change much for you, anyway.
Did you have to say that now?
No matter what you say, it's your responsibility.
Please, Taichi! Not you too!
I'm done for!
I don't want to be held back and have to call Yui, "Yui-senpai"!
Calm down.
You'll just have to keep repeating until you become a second-year.
So you think I'm going to be held back, too!
I'm surprised we were able to get this much done in such a short amount of time.
Not to overhype this, but I think this may be our magnum opus!
This might be the first time we've ever worked so hard for a CRC activity.
Yeah.
Totally unbiased, and we've got a ton of information.
We've got a chance to win here.
The only question is...
...if all five of us can do the presentation together.
Inaba, it's okay.
Thanks.
Hey!
How's it hanging, guys?
Oh, it's you, Gossan.
Thank goodness.
What's that supposed to mean, Kiriyama?
Happy to see me, are you?
Well, aren't you cute?
Oh, please!
You're just saying that!
Wait, hearing that from you doesn't make me feel good at all.
The way you said that didn't make me feel very good either.
I'm starting to regret bringing you guys these snacks.
Uh, Gossan, you're not carrying anything.
Shoot! I forgot them in the faculty room!
Nothing helps you forget about your problems like watching an idiot at work.
Inaba, didn't your parents ever teach you to respect your teachers?
If you're done here, get lost.
I try to teach respect, but I only get disrespect in return!
You don't usually come by with snacks.
Well, you guys have been working pretty hard.
I can't favor you guys over the jazz band because of my job,
so I'll be rooting for both you guys and the jazz band.
Hard work's something that really shows.
And there'll always be a helping hand available for those who try their hardest.
So you really are a teacher, Gossan.
He has his moments.
This might be my first time seeing one of those moments.
Where's Nagase?
Did she go to the bathroom or something?
It's cold today.
Yaegashi.
What's wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
Did you get an emotion transmission from Iori earlier?
Yeah.
It was just her thinking that it's cold out today.
I wish she'd come to the club room.
Quit getting depressed at every little thing!
Remember what I told you yesterday?
You need to thrust yourself in hard!
Yeah.
We've gotta get through that presentation first.
That's more like it.
We're doing this for Iori, too.
I'm sure she'll be back to her cheerful old self in no time!
Yeah, you're right.
We're not alone.
I'll do whatever I can for Nagase.
Iori will go back to normal.
I just know it.
All we can do is wait and have faith.
No one gets it.
I've had enough.
I really have.
All of their feelings are too bright, too passionate.
I can't take it.
They're all such good people.
I don't deserve to feel what they feel.
So, Watase, how's that "I Didn't Get Chocolate from Her on Valentine's Day,
but I'll Give Fujishima-san Something on White Day and Ask Her Out" thing working for you?
Well, you see, Fujishima-san is on an important mission
to "Kick the Asses of Those Guys Who Got Chocolate but Didn't Have the Guts to Give Something in Return."
I ran into Fujishima-san last night while she was walking her dog.
He's a bulldog, but he's just so cute!
What?
I don't think bulldogs are what you'd call "cute"...
I can't let that comment slide.
Fujishima-san!
Allow me to show you in great detail just how cute bulldogs can be!
Once I'm done with you, you'll faint from just how charming my little baby is!
Here's a picture of him.
Fujishima sure is popular.
Didn't I tell you?
He's adorable!
I'm more concerned about what those three are talking about.
I always thought Iori was just pretending to be a good girl.
Super-happy, cute, natural airheads always turn out to be fake.
With the way she's acting now,
that rumor about her tricking guys into doing whatever she wants is probably true.
Could I have your attention, everyone?
I'm sure you've all noticed that Nagase's been acting pretty weird lately.
Rumors involving her are being spread, too.
They're not just rumors.
They're the truth.
I don't know what you've heard, but I'm asking you guys not to believe those rumors.
Just look at how Nagase's been acting.
Isn't that proof enough?
Yeah, totally.
She changed way too quick.
There's a reason for that!
Oh?
And what's that?
I loved Nagase.
So I came on to her!
In a way that I can't go into detail about in public!
Calm down, Yaegashi!
Are you sure you should be telling everyone this?
And I went a bit too far!
I went way too far!
Way, way too far!
Like, so way too far that I can't even describe it!
And because of that, Nagase can't trust anyone anymore!
So, basically, it's my fault that Nagase's been acting weird lately!
Nagase isn't at fault here!
Wait, so you're saying...
If that's true, then...
oh damn, this is bad!
Did he seriously try to rape her?!
Don't say any more!
But if he's telling the truth, I feel bad for Iori.
Yeah, it makes sense that she'd end up like that.
I didn't think Yaegashi-kun had it in him to do something like that.
Hey, this is your only chance to take it back and defend yourself.
No, but I—
Hi, Dad?
There's a criminal in my class.
Could you send a few cars over?
Hold on!
Wasn't your dad a high-up in the police department?
I've alerted the authorities.
But I haven't broken any laws!
Relax, it was a joke.
C'mere!
What were you trying to do back there?
I just wanted to stop the rumors.
Well, I know that.
I thought that if someone else was to blame for Nagase's behavior,
the rumors would settle down, and maybe she'd get some sympathy.
I know that, too.
We can't tell anyone about Balloon Vine,
so the only thing that came to mind was saying that I came on to her.
I'm asking why you had to make it your fault!
I couldn't think of anything else!
Okay, but raping her?!
Can I make an objection, please?!
I said I "came on" to her!
I never said I "raped" her!
That's still a god-awful choice of words.
And you didn't even solve the basic problem!
That's... true...
If you tell me you just wanted to shoulder some of her pain, I'm going to deck you.
That's not what I was thinking!
It's just that things would be easier on Nagase if the rumors stopped.
And Kiriyama said that I used to thrust a lot harder...
Kiriyama didn't do anything wrong!
No graves, physical, or capital punishment, okay?!
I didn't feel an emotion transmission.
How'd you know what I was thinking?
Your face.
Anyway, if you ever get it in your head to do something as stupid as that again, talk to me first!
Don't act on impulse!
Got it?!
Yes, ma'am.
You've been getting along very well recently.
Oh, excuse me.
Did I intrude on a little foreplay?
It wasn't foreplay!
Good work in the classroom back there.
I'll figure out a way to take Yaegashi-kun off the mark later, so don't worry.
Thanks to you, the rumors about Nagase-san will be a thing of the past soon enough.
Why didn't you do anything?
I thought you'd jump at the chance to stick your nose into this.
I spent a few sleepless nights thinking it over.
But ultimately, I decided it wasn't something I should stick my nose into.
I'm going to be the kind of class president
who watches her classmates grow and develop from afar.
Why are you trying to act like you're our mother?
Leading the class while providing individual freedom for personal growth.
That's what I want to do.
Though I will lend assistance when necessary.
We don't need it.
There's nothing that the two of us can't do!
There's a lot of things we can't do.
Ready to admit you're wrong?
I haven't done anything wrong.
You still think you're hot shit?
I bet you told Yaegashi-kun to say those things in front of the class.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know your Cultural Whatever Club and the jazz band are competing to keep your moderator.
And?
Why don't you lose on purpose?
You're not even in the jazz band.
Oh, this is about Shiroyama-kun, isn't it?
You bitch!
Kaoru, that's just what she wants!
She was right about you, Nagase.
You do have a shitty attitude.
Let's go, Kaoru.
Seriously. Now I'm pissed off too.
Maybe we should teach her a lesson.
We could get... to...
Are you serious?
I like that.
What?
It's none of your business.
It's his fault, after all.
What are you planning?!
Man, I feel great! It's like tests exist just to make you feel this way!
You still need to take your make-ups.
That wasn't funny.
I don't need to remind you that the presentation is more important than your make-ups, do I?
Um... They're both important to me...
We've got one week until the presentation.
We just need to practice presenting until then, and we'll be set—
Why...
I put so much work into this...
Who did this?
The door was locked when we got here!
When I find the person responsible, they're dead!
Getting angry won't solve anything.
How can I stay calm after seeing this?!
Who the hell is responsible for this?!
Those assholes from the jazz band?!
No, I don't think so.
They were clocking a ton of extra practice hours.
They wouldn't do something like this.
What now?
There's nothing we can do, is there?
Let's remake it from scratch.
But the presentation's next week!
We can't make it in time!
It's physically impossible for us to reproduce the same poster in a week...
We can meet the deadline if we do something simpler.
But can we upstage the jazz band like that?
It might be an uphill battle, but...
...we haven't lost yet!
We said that we'd do everything, including Nagase's part.
Nagase will come back to us eventually.
This is where she'll come! We can't just give up!
If you think about it, our only problem is that the pamphlets won't look as pretty.
We just need to focus on the content and how to go about presenting it.
I see.
You're right!
All right!
Moping around won't solve anything!
All we can do is face forward and march!
I'm going to beat the part of myself that got discouraged!
Looking cool, Yui!
You mean "cute"!
Okay, let's set aside finding out who did this and get to work.
But as soon as we're done with the presentation, I'm hunting those assholes down.
I'll follow them to Hell itself if I have to.
We should think of a way to keep our work safe so they can't sabotage us again.
We can keep our work at home.
And we'll need to report this to Gotou—
Nagase?
Unforgivable!
I'll kill you!
You brought other people into this! I'll never forgive you, even if you beg!
You will cry! You will scream!
You will suffer for what you've done!
Huh? What is it?
An emotion transmission from Iori?
You guys stay here!
Wouldn't it be better if Kiriyama and Aoki came with us?
No, I want to keep this between the two of us and her.
The emotion we got from her wasn't exactly a good one.
No kidding.
Oh, Fujishima?
Thanks. I owe you for this.
What'd she say?
She gave me Setouchi's phone number.
I'm busy. What do you want?
Someone's after your life. Do you know why?
I don't know anything.
I didn't do anything.
I found you!
I'll kill you!
Stop, Nagase!
Calm down, Iori!
Don't stop me!
I'm going to kill that bitch!
I'm going to kill her!
Get out of here, Setouchi! Hurry!
Don't stop me!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's all my fault!
I'm so sorry!
Why did it have to come to this?
Iori, can we try talking again?
I won't let you get away this time.
The last time we talked, I asked you to tell me what you felt from your heart.
I've come to realize that that was too one-sided, so let's make this fair.
I want you to share your pain with me.
In exchange, I'll share some of my pain with you.
I'll practically die of embarrassment.
So, whether you want to or not, you're going to tell us why you're acting this way.
Isn't that the same thing I did with you?
Got a problem with that?
A huge one!
And your logic is flawed!
I'm talking to Iori right now!
If you're just going to bitch and moan, get the hell out!
Anyway, I'm going to tell you something embarrassing.
And in front of the guy I love.
This is the epitome of embarrassing!
As you know, I'm in love with Taichi.
That love has gotten so strong that I've started seeing him in my dreams.
Stop! Now you're making me feel embarrassed!
Just the other day, I had my first dream about doing something erotic with Taichi!
I didn't get to finish it since I woke up before we could get down to business,
but just to clarify, we were about to do it in this position!
When I woke up, I thought my heart was going to explode!
My chest hurt so bad that I couldn't breathe!
But at the same time, I didn't want it to end!
So in my frustration, I thought about Taichi as I—
Stop!
What the heck are you telling her?!
You did the same thing to me!
Shit. I'm so embarrassed. I'm gonna cry...
What do you think?!
It ended up kind of cheesy, but it was damn embarrassing, right?
You were right when you said I was selfish.
I tried to get you two together, but then I said I loved him, too.
But now I know that it was inevitable.
If I still needed everything to be proven logically,
I would never have accepted the way things are now.
But I can accept it now.
I don't need logic or proof or objective evidence anymore.
I might not be as reliable anymore, but...
That's because I have faith in myself.
If you've got a problem with that, go right ahead and tell me.
I know damn well that I'm being a wise-ass.
So you can be a wise-ass, too.
Quit moping around and come at me!
Just stop.
Just stop it already.
What's the point of this?
You're so freaking stupid!
Man, what an embarrassing confession.
The way you made it was so moving.
If I broke down and cried right now, I'm sure we'd have a nice, emotional ending to all of this.
Well, sorry to break it to you, but that's not going to happen!
I've had it up to here with all of this!
I'm so damn tired of it all!
I'm tired of feeling like I'm some tragic heroine!
How many times do I need to get killed?!
How many times do I need to be torn to shreds?!
When will it end?!
What the hell is Balloon Vine?!
How the hell does he take over people's bodies?!
Everything that's happened to us is so messed up!
How long will I have to suffer?
I've had it with this!
I can't take anymore!
I understand. It's only natural.
It's been hard on you.
I didn't know you were under that much stress.
Sorry. It's not your fault.
But that doesn't mean you can't depend on us!
We'd do anything to get the normal you—
I told you, that's not it!
What kind of "me" do you want?
I can't do it anymore!
What kind of "you" we want...
What?
Nagase...
You can just be your normal self.
You make everyone around yourself happy just by being you,
and everyone loves you—
Didn't you hear me?! I can't do it anymore!
Nagase...
I can't...
I can't be the "me" that everyone wants.
I can't make everyone love me, and I can't make everyone happy.
I'm not perfect.
What were we forcing Iori to be?
Maybe Nagase Iori was more normal and average than we all thought.
I'm actually a very dark and cold person.
But I always pretended to be bright and cheerful.
Everyone thought that "me" was fun, and I thought it was fun, too.
But I'm tired of being that ideal me.
I might've been able to pull it off if I were living a normal life,
but then Balloon Vine came along, took over my body, and nearly killed me!
And just when I thought I was safe, he came again!
I was so scared that I could die, but I tried to be the person you wanted me to be.
And then that happened, and when I hated myself so much,
he gave me a chance to redo my past.
I thought about it, but I turned it down.
I've been trying so hard.
But I can only try so many times!
Now I have to deal with this emotion transmission thing.
I was so scared of being called a liar since what I think and what I do are so different.
I didn't know what to do!
Everything went so wrong!
I wanted to do it right...
I don't care, stupid.
You called me stupid, didn't you?
You're stupid!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Sure, we expected too much out of you and didn't know it.
But you tried way too hard to live up to our expectations and pushed yourself over the edge.
That makes you stupid!
Are "can" and "can't so I'll run away" all you can do?!
Just do what you can and stop midway if you can't go on!
Why bottle up your feelings until they explode? That's the worst way of dealing with anything!
No one gives a damn how you end up or how the hell you end up that way!
It's your damn life!
Live it any damn way you want!
Don't you have anything to say, Taichi?
I...
I told you that I loved you, but I never saw the real you.
It's only natural that you'd reject me.
But now I know the ideal you and the nonideal you.
I'm saying this in hopes of it getting through to the real you.
Even if it wasn't the real you, I still fell in love with you, Nagase Iori.
Why?
I'm not the person you thought I was.
I don't care!
You're right. You aren't the person I thought you were.
But I still want to be your friend.
And I still think you're my friend.
That's enough for me.
Nothing else matters.
Could you...
give me some time to think?
I never knew Setouchi was such a bitch.
You're the one who trashed the place.
Hey, once you start, it's practically therapeutic.
Who'd we hit again? The Cultural Research Club?
Poor bastards...
We fucked up their room good.
It was just a bunch of paper, anyway.
So it was you!
You fucking assholes!
Who the hell are—
You—
Guys, help me out here.
Save me!
Inaba!
Taichi!
We'll save you!
If anything ever happened to you...
Just let me say one last thing.
I'm glad I fell in love with you.